Guide to the Tim Smith Collection on The Saint MSS.418
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Sound recordings on disc, 1973-2000, undated
  - On The Beach (Special Extended Remix) -- Rea, Chris, 1986 (Box 17)
  - Send Me An Angel (Curb Dance Mix) -- Real Life, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Send Me An Angel (Curb Dance Mix) -- Real Life, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Beat The Street -- Redd, Sharon, 1982 (Box 17)
  - In The Name Of Love -- Redd, Sharon, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Never Give You Up -- Redd, Sharon, Undated (Box 17)
  - In The Name Of Love -- Redd, Sharon, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Never Give You Up -- Redd, Sharon, Undated (Box 17)
  - Love Don't Come No Stronger -- Reeves, Martha, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Keep On Holding On -- Reynolds, Margaret, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Keep On Holding On -- Reynolds, Margaret, 1982 (Box 17)
  - I Just Don't Have The Heart -- Richard, Cliff, 1989 (Box 17)
  - I Just Don't Have The Heart (Remix) -- Richard, Cliff, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Lean On You (Extended Mix) -- Richard, Cliff, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Lean On You (Extended Mix) -- Richard, Cliff, 1989 (Box 17)
  - My Pretty One -- Richard, Cliff, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Some People (Extended Version) -- Richard, Cliff, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Some People (Extended Version) -- Richard, Cliff, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Stronger Than That (Extended Version) -- Richard, Cliff, 1989 (Box 18)
  - All Night Long -- Richie, Lionel, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Don't Talk Just Kiss (Dick's 12") -- Right Said Fred, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Savage Lover -- Ring, The, 1979 (Box 18)
  - And The Beat Goes On -- Ripple, 1999 (Box 18)
  - African Queens -- Ritchie Family, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Everlasting Love -- Robinson, Vicki Sue, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Everlasting Love -- Robinson, Vicki Sue, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Everlasting Love (DX) -- Robinson, Vicki Sue, 1983 (Box 18)
  - To Sir With Love (DX) -- Robinson, Vicki Sue, 1983 (Box 18)
  - To Sir With Love -- Robinson, Vicki Sue, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Turn The Beat Around -- Robinson, Vicki Sue, Undated (Box 18)
  - I Want You -- Rofo, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Rofo's Theme (Let's Go) -- Rofo, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Have A Cigar -- Rosebud, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Pieces of Ice -- Ross, Diana, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Swept Away (DX) -- Ross, Diana, 1984 (Box 18)
  - The Boss -- Ross, Diana, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Everybody's Free (Italia) -- Rozalla, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Hold On To My Love -- Ruffin, Jimmy, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Hold On To My Love (Robbie Leslie Remix) -- Ruffin, Jimmy, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Oh World (Extended Mix) -- Rutherford, Paul, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Oh World (Delerious) -- Rutherford, Paul, 1989 (Box 18)
  - By Your Side -- Sade, Undated (Box 18)
  - Hang On To Your Love -- Sade, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Is It A Crime -- Sade, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Never As Good As The First Time (Extended Mix) -- Sade, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Sweetest Taboo -- Sade, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Your Love Is King -- Sade, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Boy Is Crying -- Saint Etienne, Undated (Box 18)
  - How We Used To Live -- Saint Etienne, Undated (Box 18)
  - Je T'Aime -- Saint Tropez, Undated (Box 18)
  - Let's Hang On -- Salazar, 1980 (Box 18)
  - The Mystery of Love (Classic Club) -- Salinas, Joy, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Everlasting Love -- Sandra, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Don't Let Me Be Misunderstood -- Santa Esmeralda, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Say It Again (John Jellybean Benitez Mix) -- Santana, 1985 (Box 18)
  - I Am Alive -- Saphir, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Come On Dance, Dance -- Saturday Night Band, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Must Be The Music -- Secret Weapon, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Maniac -- Sembello, Michael, 1983 (Box 18)
  - I Hear Thunder -- Seventh Avenue, 1984 (Box 18)
  - I Hear Thunder (Remix) -- Seventh Avenue, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Full Of Fire -- Shalamar, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Give Me Tonight -- Shannon, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Always -- Shaw, Lisa, 2000 (Box 18)
  - Love Dancin' -- Shaw, Marlena, Undated (Box 18)
  - Give Me Just A Little More Time -- Clemmons, Angela (bw Marlena Shaw), Undated (Box 18)
  - Touch Me In The Morning -- Shaw, Marlena, 1979 (Box 18)
  - The Beast In Me -- Silence featuring Gordon Grody, 1984 (Box 18)
  - The Beast In Me -- Silence featuring Gordon Grody, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Mission To Venus -- Silver Connection, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Him -- Simone, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Something Got Me Started -- Simply Red, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Stars -- Simply Red, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Let's Face The Music And Dance -- Sinatra, Frank, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Hitchin' A Ride -- Sinitta, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Thinking About Your Love -- Skipworth & Turner, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Sound Of My Heart -- Sleeping Lions, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Sound Of My Heart -- Sleeping Lions, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Don't Leave Me This Way -- Slip, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Dancer -- Soccio, Gino, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Remember -- Soccio, Gino, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Tainted Love/Where Did Our Love Go -- Soft Cell, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Boogie Fund -- Solar Flare, 1978 (Box 19)
  - You Make Me Feel Mighty Real -- Somerville, Jimmy, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Back To Life -- Soul II Soul, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Save Your Love For Me -- Space, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Save Your Love For Me (A1) / Magic Fly (A2) -- Space, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Tender Force -- Space, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Gold (Extended Version) -- Spandau Ballet, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Gold (Extended Version) -- Spandau Ballet, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Beat The Clock -- Sparks, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Just Got Back From Heaven -- Sparks, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Symptoms Of True Love -- Spencer, Tracie, 1988 (Box 19)
  - In Private -- Springfield, Dusty, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Dancing In The Dark (Blaster Mix) -- Springstein, Bruce, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Coming Out Of Hiding -- Stanley, Pamela, 1983 (Box 19)
  - I Don't Want To Talk About It -- Stanley, Pamela, 1983 (Box 19)
  - If Looks Could Kill -- Stanley, Pamela, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Rhiannon -- Stanley, Pamela, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Stranger (In A Strange Land) -- Stanley, Pamela & Paul Parker, 1986 (Box 19)
  - This Is The Right Time (Extended Remix) -- Stansfield, Lisa, 1989 (Box 19)
  - This Is The Right Time (Extended Version) -- Stansfield, Lisa, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Victim -- Staton, Candi, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Young Hearts Run Free -- Staton, Candi, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Do It Again -- Steely Dan, Undated (Box 19)
  - Got You Where I Want You Babe -- Stereo Fun, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Got You Where I Want You Babe -- Stereo Fun, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Siempre Hay Amor [Love is in the Air] (Instrumental) -- Stevens, Martin, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Dirty Cash -- Stevie V, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Dirty Cash -- Stevie V, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Desert Rose -- Sting, Undated (Box 19)
  - If You Love Somebody (Dance Mix) -- Sting, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Straight Ahead -- Straker Band, Nick, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Love Is In Control (Finger On The Trigger) Dance Remix -- Summer, Donna, 1982 (Box 19)
  - I Feel Love -- Summer, Donna, 1977 (Box 19)
  - The Wanderer -- Summer, Donna, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Hot Stuff -- Summer, Donna, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Love's About To Change My Heart (PWL 12") -- Summer, Donna, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Love's About To Change My Heart (C&C 12") -- Summer, Donna, 1989 (Box 19)
  - She Works Hard For The Money (Special Long Version) -- Summer, Donna, 1983 (Box 19)
  - She Works Hard For The Money (Special Long Version) -- Summer, Donna, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Theme From The Deep (Down, Deep Inside) -- Summer, Donna, 1977 (Box 19)
  - This Time I Know It's For Real -- Summer, Donna, 1989 (Box 19)
  - MacArthur Park Suite -- Summer, Donna, 1978 (Box 19)
  - I Love You -- Summer, Donna, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Higher -- Surreal Fields, Undated (Box 20)
  - This 'N That -- Surreal Fields, Undated (Box 20)
  - Computer Music -- Suzi Q, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Computer Music -- Suzi Q, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Harmony -- Suzi Q, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Breakout -- Swing Out Sister, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Breakout -- Swing Out Sister, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Twilight World (12" Remix) -- Swing Out Sister, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Twilight World (Superb Superb Mix) -- Swing Out Sister, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Band of Gold -- Sylvester, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Be With You -- Sylvester, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Do You Wanna Funk -- Sylvester, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Don't Stop -- Sylvester, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Don't Stop -- Sylvester, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Stars -- Sylvester, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Living For The City -- Sylvester, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Loving Is Really My Game -- Sylvester, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Take Me To Heaven -- Sylvester, 1984 (Box 20)
  - You Make Me Feel Mighty Real -- Sylvester, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Dance (Disco Heat) - Special 12" Disco Mix -- Sylvester, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Pillow Talk -- Sylvia, 1973 (Box 20)
  - Lay It On Me -- Sylvia, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Heart and Soul -- T'Pau, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Falling In Love -- Taleesa, 1996 (Box 20)
  - Time It's Time -- Talk Talk, 1984 (Box 20)
  - It's My Life -- Talk Talk, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Why Is It So Hard? (U.S. Remix - Extended Version) -- Talk Talk, 1984 (Box 20)
  - My Forbidden Lover -- Tapps, 1983 (Box 20)
  - My Forbidden Lover (Megamix) -- Tapps, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Runaway (With My Love) -- Tapps, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Boogie Oogie Oogie -- Taste of Honey, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Don't Take Away The Music -- Tavares, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Don't Take Away The Music (Hands Off The Music Mix) -- Tavares, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Come Back To Me -- Taylor, Sean, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Everybody Wants To Rule The World (Extended Mix) -- Tears For Fears, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Everybody Wants To Rule The World (Instrumental) -- Tears For Fears, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Everybody Wants To Rule The World (Urban Mix) -- Tears For Fears, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Can We Try Again -- Technique, 1983 (Box 20)
  - (Looking For Someone To Love) Tonight -- Technique, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Heaven To Me -- Technique, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Devotion (Club Mix) -- Ten City, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Devotion (Club Mix) -- Ten City, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Freedom -- Thanya, 1982 (Box 20)
  - The Bull -- Mike Theodore Orchestra, 1977 (Box 20)
  - High Energy -- Thomas, Evelyn, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Masquerade -- Thomas, Evelyn, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Reflections -- Thomas, Evelyn, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Rescue Me -- Thomas, Sybil, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Too Hot For Love -- THP Orchestra, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Twist In My Sobriety -- Tikaram, Tanita, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Endless Road -- Time Bandits, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Endless Road (I Want You To Know My Love) -- Time Bandits, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Disco Inferno -- Turner, Tina, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Let's Stay Together -- Turner, Tina, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Let's Stay Together -- Turner, Tina, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Look Me In The Heart -- Turner, Tina, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Nutbush City Limits (Nutbush City '91 Mix) -- Turner, Tina, 1991 (Box 20)
  - Face To Face - Heart To Heart -- Twins, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Wiggle It (Club) -- Two In A Room, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Wiggle It (Club) -- Two In A Room, 1990 (Box 20)
  - I Got The Feeling (12") -- Two Tons of Fun, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Earth Can Be Just Like Heaven -- Two Tons of Fun, 1980 (Box 21)
  - I'd Like To Get Closer -- USA-European Connection (Boris Midney), 1979 (Box 21)
  - Come Into My Heart | Good Loving -- USA-European Connection (Boris Midney), 1978 (Box 21)
  - Beautiful Place -- van Dyk, Paul, 1996 (Box 21)
  - The Best Things In Life Are Free -- Vandross, Luther and Janet Jackson, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Sentimentally Its You -- Vaness, Theo, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Upside Down (Long Version) -- Vanessa, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Upside Down (Long Version) -- Vanessa, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Mission Impossible Theme -- Vasquez, Junior, 1996 (Box 21)
  - Heartbeat (US Remix) -- Vee, Vivien, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Tom's Diner (12" Mix) -- Vega, Suzanne, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Got To Have Your Love -- Velvette, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Baby Won't You Dance With Me -- Vera, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Macho Man -- Village People, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Fire Island -- Village People, 1977 (Box 21)
  - YMCA -- Village People, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Love Buzz -- Voggue, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Dancin' The Night Away -- Voggue, 1981 (Box 21)
  - From East To West (Album Version) -- Voyage, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Souvenirs -- Voyage, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Souvenirs -- Voyage, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Souvenirs (Power) -- Voyage, 1983 (Box 21)
  - No One In The World -- W.F.O., 1993 (Box 21)
  - High Above the Clouds -- Walden, Narada Michael, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Reach Out -- Walden, Narada Michael, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Thinking of You -- Walsh, Maureen, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Ring My Bell -- Ward, Anita, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Heaven (Heavenly Club) -- Washington, Sarah, 1996 (Box 21)
  - Heaven (Fathers Vocal) -- Washington, Sarah, 1996 (Box 21)
  - Take A Chance On Me -- Waterfront Home, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Take A Chance On Me -- Waterfront Home, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Gypsy Woman (She's Homeless) -- Waters, Crystal, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Gypsy Woman (She's Homeless) -- Waters, Crystal, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Right Between The Eyes (Extended Remix) -- Wax, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Right Between The Eyes (Extended Remix) -- Wax, 1986 (Box 21)
  - It's Raining Men (Vocal) -- Weather Girls, 1982 (Box 21)
  - It's Raining Men (Instrumental) -- Weather Girls, 1982 (Box 21)
  - This Girl's Back In Town -- Welch, Raquel, 1987 (Box 21)
  - True Love Is My Destiny -- Wells, James, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Everything (Extended Mix) -- When In Rome, 1988 (Box 21)
  - The Promise (Coliseum Mix) -- When In Rome, 1988 (Box 21)
  - The Promise (Coliseum Mix) -- When In Rome, 1988 (Box 21)
  - The Promise (Coliseum Mix) -- When In Rome, 1988 (Box 21)
  - The Promise (Ollie North Mix) -- When In Rome, 1988 (Box 21)
  - I Can't Turn You Loose -- White, Anthony, 1977 (Box 21)
  - It's Ecstasy When You Lay Down Next To me -- White, Barry, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Rush Hour (Extended Remix) -- Wiedlin, Jane, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Sparks (Glenn Howard Mix) -- Wilde, Kim, 1983 (Box 21)
  - You Keep Me Hangin' On -- Wilde, Kim, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Love Story -- Williams, Andy, 1979 (Box 21)
  - War Of The Worlds -- Wayne, Jeff, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Love Is You -- Williams, Carol, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Heaven In Your Eyes -- Williams, Deniece, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Touch Me In The Morning (DX) -- Shaw, Marlena, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Secret Love (Special Remixed Version) -- Wills, Viola, 1982 (Box 22)
  - Up On The Roof -- Wills, Viola, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Both Sides Now -- Wills, Viola, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Over The Rainbow -- Wills, Viola, Undated (Box 22)
  - If You Could Read My Mind (Long Version) -- Wills, Viola, 1980 (Box 22)
  - If You Could Read My Mind (Long Version) -- Wills, Viola, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Always Something There To Remind Me (Version 1) -- Wills, Viola, 1996 (Box 22)
  - Up On The Roof (Extended Version) -- Wills, Viola, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Up On The Roof / After The Dance (Disconet) -- Wills, Viola / Michelle Lamb, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Show and Tell -- Wilson, Al, Undated (Box 22)
  - Don't Get Mad, Get Even -- Wilson, Mary, Undated (Box 22)
  - Another Sleepless Night (Classic Mix) -- Wilson, Mike, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Give Me Back My Heart -- Wright, Robin, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Give Me Back My Heart -- Wright, Robin, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Get Ready -- X-Ray Connection, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Situation -- Yazoo, 1982 (Box 22)
  - The Only Way Is Up (UK Extended Club Mix) -- Yazz, 1988 (Box 22)
  - The Only Way Is Up (UK Extended Club Mix) -- Yazz, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Oh Yeah (Dance Mix) -- Yello, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Gold Rush -- Yello, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Oh Yeah -- Yello, Undated (Box 22)
  - Behind The Mask -- Yellow Magic Orchestra, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Rydeen -- Yellow Magic Orchestra, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Lover To Lover -- Yellow, Joe, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Owner Of A Lonely Heart (Red & Blue Dance Remix) -- Yes, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Love Is In The Air -- Young, John Paul, 1977 (Box 22)
  - Hot Shot -- Young, Karen, 1978 (Box 22)
  - If Only I Could -- Youngblood, Sydney, 1989 (Box 22)
  - If Only I Could -- Youngblood, Sydney, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Head Over Heals -- Zarathustra, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Magic Nights -- Zarathustra, 1986 (Box 22)
- Stardust, 1982-1983 (Box Shared Fales 003)
- Subject Files
  - DJs, 1998-2014; FA_MSS_418_ER_1; 13.2 Megabytes in 32 computer files
  - Graebar, 2003-2014; FA_MSS_418_ER_2; 78.1 Megabytes in 12 computer files
  - Miscellaneous, 2013-2014; FA_MSS_418_ER_3; 13.7 Megabytes in 43 computer files
  - Music, 2009-2014; FA_MSS_418_ER_4; 36.1 Megabytes in 7 computer files
  - New St. Marks Baths, 2009-2014; FA_MSS_418_ER_7; 1.57 Megabytes in 2 graphics files
  - The Saint At Large, 1998-2014; FA_MSS_418_ER_5; 25.3 Megabytes in 35 computer files
  - Saint Members, 2009-2014; FA_MSS_418_ER_6; 1.71 Megabytes in 6 computer files
  - Star Field Projector, 2002-2014; FA_MSS_418_ER_8; 26.1 Megabytes in 55 graphics files
  - Trippin' on the Moon, 2009-2014; FA_MSS_418_ER_9; 1.68 Megabytes in 8 graphics files
  - William Pilkington's Last Party Photographs, 2013; FA_MSS_418_ER_10; 3.36 Megabytes in 33 graphics files